Hey everyone, what's up? Welcome to this video. I have a new Amoresi jumpsuit I want to show you.
But first let me say thank you because I noticed that a lot of you used my discount code within the last few weeks and months,
which makes me super happy. And what I also noticed is that you're buying menswear stuff by Amoresi.
I mean, of course, I can't really show you the menswear items. I can show you a few more pictures.
but I'm really happy that you use the code also to buy yourself something and yeah today I have
a new material super fine spandex which I'm going to show you and it's a really fun color
the packaging says the color is called cabbage I think it's more like a minty green I don't know
help me out here what would you call this color write it in the comments down below
and i'm going to get changed in a meanwhile this is cabbage and i don't think that the color matches
so whoever is that colorblind please rename this catsuit name it whatever after eight or something
i love after eight by the way chocolate and mint best combination ever anyway this is the catsuit
Obviously it's very very see-through. That's why I'm wearing underwear under it of course.
By the way when I say this is the safe for YouTube version because of the underwear
it does not mean that there is a non-safe for YouTube version somewhere. Although I have a
Patreon you can find a lot of additional content there. But anyway this is the super silky fabric
which means it is sheer and it is as all the Amoresi products really really soft
and smooth and so really nice spandex fabric. What I like about these catsuits
is that they have a nice cut here with a high leg seam so it looks a bit like a
fashion cut also with the back part and yeah I have a lot of other Amoresi
outfits and videos check them out they also have a sub brand called Amoti which
makes not spandex but wait a sec I'm missing something nylon they also make
nylon outfits like catsuits and gloves and ties so check that out as well I
have a video for that too and yeah of course as I said already I have a
discount code so please remember to use that I will put everything in the description text
and I hope you enjoyed this video tell me what do you think of this color would you wear it
I think it goes pretty well with my hair which is not something new but I love to say it every
time again and again and I think it's fun to wear at home to lounge around in something comfy like
this I would not wear it outside but the color is fun so I wanted to show it to you okay um that
was it I hope you enjoyed this one have a nice day see you in the next video bye